CAMILA PALADINES

Frontend Developer



(+57) 321 425 7485



Cali, Colombia



camilapaladines.netlify.app



camilapaladines27@gmail.com

ABOUT

I'm a Frontend Developer with 1+ years of experience in React and React Native. I have worked with TypeScript, Firebase, HTML, CSS, SCSS and JavaScript. I have built responsive and engaging web interfaces and mobile applications, with a focus on delivering highquality work that fits user requirements. I have a C1 level of professional English.

SKILLS

Languages

HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, TypeScript

Libraries & Frameworks

React, React Native, TailwindCSS

Tools & Platforms

Git, GitHub, Firebase, Figma, Scrum

SOCIAL



paladinescamila



paladinescamila

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Web/Mobile Developer

Piyion | June 2022 - Present

- Developed responsive web interfaces using React, TypeScript and Firebase services, creating client interactions based on the provided design specifications.
- Built a mobile application using React Native, TypeScript, SCSS and Firebase services.
- Consumed REST APIs to retrieve and display data within web and mobile applications.

Frontend Web Developer

Ninus Design & Technology | March 2022 - June 2022

- Developed responsive web interfaces using React and SCSS, creating client interactions based on provided design specifications.
- Consumed REST APIs to retrieve and display data within the application.
- Debugged and tested all functionality to ensure high quality deliverables that fit user requirements.

PROJECTS

- **Alle Shop** | E-commerce web app | React · TypeScript · TailwindCSS · Firebase
- **Calculator App** | Frontend Mentor challenge | React · TypeScript · SCSS
- **Sunnyside Agency** | Frontend Mentor challenge | React · TypeScript · SCSS
- **Card Details** | Frontend Mentor challenge | React · TypeScript · SCSS
- ◆ Space Tourism | Frontend Mentor challenge | React · TypeScript · SCSS

EDUCATION

Computer Science and Engineering

Pontificia Universidad Javeriana - Cali, Colombia | 2018 - 2022